Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-2002
Wisconsin Historical Society
- Part 5 (M85-006): Additions, 1928-2001, M85-006; 140 c.f. (138 record center cartons and 5 archives boxes)
  - Plaintiff's Evidence
    - Plaintiff's discovery production to the defendant
      - Produced 1/10/1979 (Box 110)
      - Produced 5/2/1980 (Box 110)
      - Bulletins and Pamphlets (Box 111)
      - Financial records 9/24/1980 (Box 111)
      - International Tendency (Box 112)
    - Plaintiff's publications introduced as evidence (Box 113)
    - Plaintiff correspondence regarding financial standing (Box 113)
    - Plaintiff's miscellaneous productions (Box 113)
    - Political Rights Defense Fund Support
      - 1973-1975 (Box 113)
      - 1976-1987 (Box 114)
      - 1988 (Box 115)
    - Plaintiff's production to the defendant
      - Produced 9/5/1980 (Box 115)
      - Produced 9/19/1980 (Box 115)
      - Produced 9/30/1980 (Box 115)
      - Produced 11/12/1980 (Box 115)
      - Produced 3/3/1981 (Box 115)
    - Index to plaintiff's exhibits (Box 115)
    - Plaintiff's reply to defendant's post trial memoranda (Box 115)
    - Index and summaries of plaintiff's evidence file (Box 115)
    - Plaintiff's Federal Tort Claims Act claims (Box 115)
    - Defendant's trial subpoenas (Box 115)
    - Plaintiff's trial subpoenas (Box 115)
    - Peter Camejo subpoena correspondence (Box 115)
    - Winter-Pike report (Box 115)
    - Miscellaneous indices (Box 116)
    - Marion Bustin federal tort claims (Box 116)
    - Hector Marroquin federal tort claims (Box 116)
    - Trial testimony summaries (Box 116)
    - Complaints and Mandigo affidavit (Box 116)
    - Trial plans, evidence memos, proposed findings of fact (Box 116)
    - Motions to dismiss, I-IV (Box 117)
    - Motions to dismiss, V (Box 118)
    - M. Wesley Swearingen file (Box 118)
    - Deposition notices (Box 118)
    - New York Police Department Protective Order (Box 118)
    - Attorney General Griffin Bell contempt of court proceedings (Box 119)
    - Young Socialist Alliance preliminary injunction against the FBI (Box 119)
    - V. Starr file (Box 119)
    - James Gerblick affidavit (Box 119)
    - Judge Murray Gurfein file (Box 120)
    - Government request for hearing by United States Court of Appeals, 1977 (Box 120)
    - FBI telexes supplied by field offices to head quarters regarding to informants (Box 120)
    - FBI factual data files (Box 120)
    - FBI guidelines (Box 121)
    - Miscellaneous discoveries (Box 121)
    - Motions of substitution, 1983-1986 (Box 121)
    - Injunction pleadings (Box 121)
    - Plaintiff's requests, 1973 (Box 121)
    - Discovery motions
      - 1973-1975 (Box 121)
      - 1976 (Box 122)
      - 1977 (Box 123)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 124)
    - Socialist Workers Party correspondence with the Attorney General
      - 1973-1977 (Box 125)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 126)
      - 1981-1987 (Box 127)
    - Discovery motions 1978-1979 (Box 128)
    - Trial hearings transcripts
      - 1974-1976 (Box 128)
      - 1976-1979 (Box 129)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 130)
    - Depositions taken by defendant
      - Connie Allen (Box 131)
      - Jack Barnes (Box 131)
      - John Barzman (Box 131)
      - Michael Baumann (Box 131)
      - John Benson (Box 131)
      - Peggy Brundy (Box 131)
      - Marian Bustin (Box 131)
      - Peter Camejo (Box 131)
      - Nancy Cole (Box 131)
      - Stephen H. Cooper (Box 131)
      - Kathryn Crowder (Box 131)
      - Kipp Dawson (Box 131)
      - Farrell Dobbs (Box 131)
      - Farrell Dobbs (Box 132)
      - Richard Feigenberg (Box 132)
      - Hedda Garza (Box 132)
      - Joseph Hansen (Box 132)
      - Lisa Hickler (Box 132)
      - Gus Horowitz (Box 132)
      - Arthur Hughes (Box 132)
      - Doug Jenness (Box 132)
      - Linda Jenness (Box 132)
      - Lester Lantz (Box 132)
      - Caroline Lund (Box 132)
      - Hector Marroquin (Box 132)
      - George Novack (Box 132)
      - Mohammed Oliver (Box 132)
      - Joan Paltrineri (Box 132)
      - Dave Prince (Box 133)
      - Andrew Pulley (Box 133)
      - Dick Roberts (Box 133)
      - Willie Mae Reid (Box 133)
      - Priscilla Schenk (Box 133)
      - Evelyn Sell (Box 133)
      - Bob Schwarz (Box 133)
      - Ed Shaw (Box 133)
      - Barry Sheppard (Box 133)
      - Syd Stapleton (Box 133)
      - Morris Starsky (Box 133)
      - Tony Thomas (Box 134)
      - Shannon Trujillo (Box 134)
      - Marilyn Vogt (Box 134)
      - Mary-Alice Waters (Box 134)
      - Tim Wohlforth (Box 134)
    - Depositions taken by plaintiff
      - Rene Amaya (Box 134)
      - George Baxtrum (Box 134)
      - John V. Clark (Box 134)
      - Richard Cotter (Box 134)
      - John Donahue (Box 134)
      - Lieutenant Timothy Dowdine (Box 134)
      - Godfrey England (Box 134)
      - Joseph Furrer (Box 134)
      - William Gardner (Box 135)
      - Max Geldman (Box 135)
      - Arthur Greene (Box 135)
      - Paul Haefner (Box 135)
      - Donald Harmon (Box 135)
      - George Herbert (Box 135)
      - Edward Heisler (Box 135)
      - Raymond Jackson (Box 135)
      - Clarence Kelley (Box 135)
      - James Kott (Box 135)
      - Robert Lang (Box 135)
      - Mary Lawton (Box 135)
      - Joseph McMahon (Box 135)
      - John Malone (Box 135)
      - Albert Maretta (Box 135)
      - James Mastrovito (Box 136)
      - Brinkley Messick (Box 136)
      - John Mitchell (Box 136)
      - John Neal (Box 136)
      - James Nilson (Box 136)
      - John O'Brien (Box 136)
      - Richard Ober (Box 136)
      - Robert O'Neill (Box 136)
      - Timothy Redfearn (Box 136)
      - Raymond Ruckel (Box 136)
      - Cornelius Scully (Box 136)
      - Robert Shackelford (Box 136)
      - Thomas Stewart (Box 136)
      - Gary Stoops (Box 136)
      - William Sullivan (Box 136)
      - Lieutenant Bruce Van Bille (Box 136)
      - William Wharton (Box 136)
      - Plaintiff's memo in support of the motion for awarding of expenses (Box 136)
  - Trial Documents
    - Index to the trial record (Box 136)
    - Minor items 4/3/1981-6/25/1981 (Box 136)
    - Presentations
      - COINTELPRO (Box 137)
      - Church Committee (Box 137)
      - FBI interviews (Box 137)
      - Civil Service Commission (Box 137)
      - Secret Affidavit (Box 137)
      - COINTELPRO-Socialist Workers Party elections (Box 137)
      - Breitel Report (Box 137)
      - CIA presence (Box 137)
      - Peterson report (Box 137)
      - Army (Box 137)
      - Navy and Air Force (Box 137)
      - Initiation of Investigation (Box 137)
      - United Secretariat Minutes (Box 137)
    - Trial witness testimony
      - Kim Allen (Box 137)
      - Rene Amaya (Box 137)
      - Jack Barnes (Box 137)
      - George Baxtrum (Box 137)
      - Glenn Bertness (Box 137)
      - Robert Blakey (Box 137)
      - Edgar Best (Box 137)
      - George Breitman (Box 138)
      - Herbert Brownell (Box 138)
      - Stephen Cohen (Box 138)
      - Kathryn Crowder (Box 138)
      - Nancy Cole (Box 138)
      - Wayne Dean (Box 138)
      - Clifton DeBerry (Box 138)
      - Thiago DeMello (Box 138)
      - Ralph Desimone (Box 138)
      - Farrell Dobbs (Box 138)
      - Ken Evenhuis (Box 138)
      - Thomas Filkins (Box 138)
      - Irving Fishman (Box 138)
      - Kathy Fitzgerald (Box 138)
      - Hedda Garza (Box 138)
      - Catarino Garza (Box 138)
      - Gary Greenhalgh (Box 138)
      - Arthur Greene (Box 138)
      - Fred Halstead (Box 138)
      - Russell Harding (Box 138)
      - Lieutenant George Hebert (Box 138)
      - Edward Heisler (Box 138)
      - Lisa Hickler (Box 139)
      - Stephen Horne (Box 139)
      - John Hotis (Box 139)
      - Linda Jenness (Box 139)
      - Merrill Kelly (Box 139)
      - Laurel Kelly (Box 139)
      - Robert Keuch (Box 139)
      - Joseph Knazik (Box 139)
      - James Kott (Box 139)
      - Robert Kyanko (Box 139)
      - Mary Lawton (Box 139)
      - Hannah Levin (Box 139)
      - Howard Leibow (Box 139)
      - George Litzenberg (Box 139)
      - Caroline Lund (Box 139)
      - Charles Mandigo (Box 139)
      - Hector Marroquin (Box 139)
      - Mel Mason (Box 139)
      - Joseph McMahon (Box 139)
      - Norman McCabe (Box 139)
      - Dirk Merrill (Box 139)
      - Laura Miller (Box 139)
      - John O'Brien (Box 139)
      - Gregory Oswald (Box 140)
      - Jose Perez (Box 140)
      - J.G. Perkins (Box 140)
      - Paul Philip (Box 140)
      - Frederick Phillips (Box 140)
      - Milorad Popov (Box 140)
      - David Prince (Box 140)
      - Andrew Pulley (Box 140)
      - William Ratliff (Box 140)
      - Willie Mae Reid (Box 140)
      - Will Reissner (Box 140)
      - Olga Rodriguez (Box 140)
      - Priscilla Schenk (Box 140)
      - Michael Schlosser (Box 140)
      - Larry Seigle (Box 140)
      - Cornelius Scully (Box 140)
      - Evelyn Sell (Box 140)
      - Gabrielle Shelley (Box 140)
      - Barry Sheppard (Box 140)
      - Joseph Sizoo (Box 140)
      - Willis Smith (Box 140)
      - Morris Starsky (Box 140)
      - Gary Stoops (Box 140)
      - Gary Stoops (Box 141)
      - William Sullivan (Box 141)
      - Thomas Walczykowski (Box 141)
      - Susan Wald (Box 141)
      - W. Raymond Wannall (Box 141)
      - Mary-Alice Waters (Box 141)
      - Steve Wattenmaker (Box 141)
      - Thomas West (Box 141)
      - Robert Wilkinson (Box 141)
    - Plaintiff's answer to the defendant's post trial memo regarding to FTCA jurisdiction (Box 141)
    - Legal record for the United States Court of Appeals, Contained in 10 volumes is a copy of the entire legal record (Docket No. 78-6114) prepared in 1978 for the Court of Appeals to review the decision of Federal District Court Judge Thomas Griesa earlier that year declaring U.S. Attorney General Griffin Bell to be in contempt of court for refusing to produce files requested by the SWP's attorneys on 18 FBI informers.
      - Volumes I-V (Box 141)
      - Volumes VI-IX (Box 142)
      - Volume X, Supplementary index (Box 142)
- Part 6 (M92-173): Additions, undated, M92-173; 1 film, 40 discs, and 142 tape recordings
  Paper documentation received in this accession has been microfilmed and processed. Remaining under this accession number are disc and tape recordings (mainly speeches and lectures by SWP leaders) and one film. The tapes have been assigned call number Audio 1275A. Two of the tapes from this accession are cataloged with Part 1, the Original Collection portion of the collection.
- Part 7 (M93-249): Additions, 1953-1972, M93-249; 12 tape recordings
  Additional tape recordings including material by James P. Cannon from the debate during the early 1950s with the Cochran faction, plus talks, lectures, speeches, and discussions, 1953-1972. The tapes have been assigned call number Audio 1275A.
- Part 8 (M2005-027): Additions, 1929, 1940-2002, M2005-027; 6.2 c.f. (4 record center cartons and 6 archives boxes)
  Additions, 1929, 1940-2002, consisting of campaign materials, documents relating to Federal Election Commission disclosure, issues of the Pathfinder Sales Newsletter, Political Committee, Political Bureau, and National Committee minutes, a Communist League of America silk banner with hand-stitching, political buttons, and various anti-war materials.
  - Election Campaigns
    - Campaign Platforms
      - 1948-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - National Campaign, 1996
      - Campaign Tours (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Index to Militant Coverage (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - International Trip (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Local Campaigns (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - State Campaigns (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Petition Drives (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Press Coverage (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Media Material (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Web Page (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Opponents/Rightists (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Finances (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - List of 1996 Candidate and Vote Totals (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - National Campaign, 1992
      - Campaign Tours (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Index to Militant Coverage (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - International Trips (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Local Campaigns (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Press and Other Material (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Referenda, Positions Taken On (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Statements and Brochures (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Youth for Warren and Debates (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - National Campaign Committee
      - Minutes, 1988-1966 (Box 1, Folder 25-28)
      - Progress Report, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - State Campaigns
      - Press Coverage, 1997, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
      - Statements and Flyers, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania Statewide Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - California Statewide Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Disclosure
      - Washington State, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Notice of Expiration of Disclosure Exemption, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Appeal for Exemption, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Exemption, 1990 Advisory Opinion and Memo on 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Exemption, List of Materials for 1996 Advisory Opinion (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Extension of Federal Exemption, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Local Exemption Cases, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Miami, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - Federal Consent Decree, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Socialist Action, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Hall-Tyner Decision, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Disclosure Exemption
      - Memo on 2002 Expiration Date of Disclosure Exemption (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Index to Militant Articles, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Local Disclosure Cases
        - Arizona, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
        - Florida, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 49)
        - Iowa, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 50)
        - Los Angeles, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Brown Decision, 1981
        - Articles (Box 1, Folder 52)
        - Decision (Box 1, Folder 53)
        - Southern Ohio District Court Appeal (Box 1, Folder 54)
      - SWP/YSA and CISPES (Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador), FOIA Requests, 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - Consent Decree, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence regarding Exemption Extension (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - Correspondence with ACLU (American Civil Liberties Union) (Box 1, Folder 58)
      - Criteria for Exemption: SWP Memorandum of Law, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Exhibits for 1990 Exemption Appeal (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - FEC (Federal Election Commission) Correspondence regarding Exemption, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Federal Exemption, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - 1990 Advisory Opinion (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - Appeal for Exemption, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Exhibits for 1996 Exemption Appeal (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
      - 1996 Advisory Opinion (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - New York Case
      - FEC Reports, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Financial Reports, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ballot Fights
      - Index to SWP Court Rulings (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Ballot Fights, General (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Georgia: Jenness, Linda v. Little, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Michigan: SWP v. Hare, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Georgia: Jenness v. Fortson, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Texas: SWP v. Welch, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Massachusetts: Baird v. Davoren, SWP v. Davoren, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Florida: Jenness v. Miller, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Illinois: SWP of Illinois v. Ogilvie, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Massachusetts: SWP and Florence Luscomb v. Davoren, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - California: SWP v. March Fong Eu, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Illinois: Board of Elections v. SWP, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Louisiana: SWP v. Hardy, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Michigan: SWP v. Secretary of State, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Ohio, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Washington: SWP v. Munro, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - West Virginia (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - West Virginia, Other Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Arizona, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Florida, 1992, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Massachusetts, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Nebraska, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Boston, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Delaware, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - New Alliance Lawsuit
        - Summary of Case (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - New York State Response (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - SWP Legal Briefs (Box 2, Folder 33)
        - SWP Campaign Statement (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Write-in Cases
      - Hawaii
        - Burdick Appeal Brief, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - Correspondence with Edward Copeland (Box 2, Folder 36)
        - Court Decision, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
        - Denial of Appeal, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
        - Other Amicus Briefs, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
        - Press Coverage, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
        - SWP Amicus Briefs, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Maryland: Write-ins and Filing Fees, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - North Carolina (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Electoral Policy
    - Campaigns
      - Mason Campaign (1982), Manuel Report (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Peace and Freedom Party: Debate in SWP, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Communist Election Campaigns
      - Composition of Slate (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - On the Job, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Critical Support
      - Communist Labor Party, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Smith Campaign, San Francisco (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Labor Party Club Discussion, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Police Review Boards (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Referenda
      - California anti-crime (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Abortion Rights, Washington, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
      - California Budget, Transfer Payments, Entitlements and Social Wage, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Corporate Farming (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Death with Dignity, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Education-School Vouchers, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - ERA, Iowa, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Family Farm Amendment, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Gambling, Georgia Lottery, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - History of (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Jobs with Peace, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Nuclear, Rocky Flats Conversion, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Nuclear Weapons Conversion, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Party Organizer (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Pittsburgh Housing, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Police Review Boards, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Rent Control (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Taxes
        - Dallas, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        - Marx, Engels, Lenin on (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Minutes, 1982-2001
    - Pathfinder Executive Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1-16)
    - Publishing Executive Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 17-27)
    - Youth Work Executive Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
    - YSA National Executive Committee, 1986-1989
      - 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 30-34)
      - 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
    - Secretariat Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7-11)
    - Political Bureau Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 12-17)
    - Political Committee (PB/PC/NC), 2001
      - January-June (Box 5, Folder 18-23)
      - June-December (Box 6, Folder 1-9)
    - Information Bulletin, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Index of Minutes (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Anti-War Materials and Newsletters
    - Militant press release, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1990 campaign platforms (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Chicago mayoral campaign, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Local campaign platforms, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Education for Socialists, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - National Campaign committee, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - State campaigns summary, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - International Socialist Review, 1964, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Fair Play for Cuba Committee: Legal Briefs (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Materials on Lumpenproletariat (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Harvard Archives photocopy: Speech Notes and Manual, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Socialist Workers Party Chronology Resolutions On the Character of the War, and the Perspectives of Fourth Internationalists, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Internal Bulletin, The Spanish Revolution (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Socialist Writings (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Young Socialist Alliance (YSA): Student Peace Union (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bring the Troops Home (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - National Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam (NCC) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Fort Hood (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Student Mobilization Committee (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Black Freedom Movement (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Cuban Press Survey (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - New York Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Fair Play Chapter Notes (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Fair Play for Cuba Committee: Kansas, Philadelphia, Michigan (Box 9, Folder 10-12)
    - 1960s (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Canada-Bulletin (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Personal JPC: Jeanne Morgan drawings (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Communist League of America silk banner (WHi image ID 75173) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Political buttons for SWP elections and candidates, end the draft, support equal rights amendment, and other campaigns (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Pathfinder Sales Newsletter, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)